

# PERSONAL DETAILS

Name	Danish Shaik	
D.O.B	27 August 1997	
Web	http://www.dshaik.com	
Contact	+1(408) 207-8836	
Email	✓ shaik.danish97@gmail.com	

# EDUCATION

High School	Monta Vista High School
Middle College	De-Anza College
<b>X</b> AWARDS	
Third Place	Photo Hack Day (iMaze)-Featured on TechCrunch
Finalist	Brim (Outside Hacks)



#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Flipboard**

Jul 2014 - Sept 2014

# **Engineering Intern**

Worked as a Software Developer Intern on the Platforms Team. Used several external and internal frameworks to build an internal analytics dashboard. Worked on an internal interface to increase productivity of customer-support team. An interface for dealing with customer issues and flagged items coupled with a robust analytics system with notifications and warnings.

#### Softech

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013

#### Web Dev Intern

Worked as a Software Engineering Intern on Web Development Team. Worked on Front-End for Company web presence. Used technologies include jOuery, Bootstrap, and Backbone.js to create a seamless beautiful responsive webpage.

#### dshaik.com

Jan 2012 - May 2013

## Freelance Developer

Met with clients to define aesthetic and functional specifications. Analyzed client's business objectives and directions for the web in terms of product positioning, branding, target audience or markets and web traffic generation. Worked with a variety of businesses in order to create a web presence for their brand.



## **PROJECTS**

#### Brim

An iOS mobile application, which utilizes Bluetooth Low Energy in order to notify you when you are on the brink of losing your friends. Brim sends a push notification when your friends move out of range, as well showing you a realtime map displaying your friends' location.

#### Spark

Spark is a roommate discovery app that suggest potential roommates. Based on similarities between users, the app allows the user to anonymously like or pass them. If two users like each other then it results in a "match" and Spark introduces the two users by opening a chat.



#### **PROFILE**



- 📝 twitter.com/danshaik
- www.dshaik.com
- (in) linkedin.com/in/danishshaik

Hello! I'm Danish, a 16 year old web developer based in Cupertino, CA.

I love coding, designing, ping pong, and working on neat projects. I attend De Anza College, through a Middle College Program taking college level courses as a senior in High School.



#### SKILLS



#### Languages

JavaScript HTML CSS3 C++



# Technologies

Node.js Jade EJS (Embedded JavaScript)



## Frameworks

Express.js d3.js jQuery Backbone.js Angular.js Bootstrap Foundation



#### **Platforms**

Web Chrome App Store Leap Motion